[
    {
        "question": "The CSS property used to control the element's font-size is__________",
        "answer_1": "font-size",
        "answer_2": "text-size",
        "answer_3": "text-style",
        "answer_4": "None",
        "right_answer": "font-size"
    },
    {
        "question": "The HTML attribute used to define the internal stylesheet is___________",
        "answer_1": "style",
        "answer_2": "<style>",
        "answer_3": "<link>",
        "answer_4": "<script>",
        "right_answer": "<style>"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following CSS property is used to set the background image of an element?",
        "answer_1": "background-color",
        "answer_2": "background-image",
        "answer_3": "background-attachment",
        "answer_4": "None",
        "right_answer": "background-image"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to display the hyperlinks without any underline?",
        "answer_1": "a {decoration : no-underline;}",
        "answer_2": "a {text-decoration : underline;}",
        "answer_3": "a {text-decoration : none;}",
        "answer_4": "None",
        "right_answer": "a {text-decoration : none;}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to make the background-color of all paragraph elements to yellow?",
        "answer_1": "all {background-color : yellow;}",
        "answer_2": "p {background-color : #yellow;}",
        "answer_3": "p {background-color : yellow;}",
        "answer_4": "all p {background-color : #yellow;}",
        "right_answer": "p {background-color : yellow;}"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following property is used as the shorthand property for the padding properties?",
        "answer_1": "padding-right",
        "answer_2": "padding-left",
        "answer_3": "padding",
        "answer_4": "All of the above",
        "right_answer": "padding"
    },
    {
        "question": " How to select the elements with the class name “example”?",
    "answer_1": "example",
    "answer_2": "#example",
    "answer_3": "Class example",
    "answer_4": ".example",
        "right_answer": ".example"
    },
    {
        "question": "The CSS property used to make the text bold is___________",
    "answer_1": "weight: bold",
    "answer_2": "font-weight: bold",
    "answer_3": "style: bold",
    "answer_4": "font: bold",
        "right_answer": "font-weight: bold"
    },
    {
        "question": "The property in CSS used to change the background color of an element is_____________",
    "answer_1": "background-color",
    "answer_2": "color",
    "answer_3": "bgcolor",
    "answer_4": "None",
        "right_answer": "background-color"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following syntax is correct in CSS to make each word of a sentence start with a capital letter?",
    "answer_1": "transform: capitalize;",
    "answer_2": "text-style: capital;",
    "answer_3": "text-transform: capital;",
    "answer_4": "text-transform: capitalize;",
        "right_answer": "text-transform: capitalize;"
    },
    {
        "question": "CSS stands for _________",
        "answer_1": "Color and style sheets",
        "answer_2": "Cascading style sheet",
        "answer_3": "Cascade style sheets",
        "answer_4": "None",
        "right_answer": "Cascading style sheet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax for referring the external style sheet?",
        "answer_1": "<style src = “example.css” >",
        "answer_2": "<style src = example.css>",
        "answer_3": "<stylesheet> example.css </stylesheet>",
        "answer_4": "<link rel=”stylesheet” type=”text/css” href=”example.css”>",
        "right_answer": "<link rel=”stylesheet” type=”text/css” href=”example.css”>"
    },
    {
        "question": "The CSS property used to specify whether the text is written in the horizontal or vertical direction?",
        "answer_1": "text-indent",
        "answer_2": "writing-mode",
        "answer_3": "word-break",
        "answer_4": "None",
        "right_answer": "writing-mode"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to select all paragraph elements in a div element?",
        "answer_1": "p",
        "answer_2": "div p",
        "answer_3": "div#p",
        "answer_4": "div ~p",
        "right_answer": "div p"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following CSS property is used to add shadows to the text?",
        "answer_1": "text-stroke",
        "answer_2": "text-decoration",
        "answer_3": "text-shadow",
        "answer_4": "text-overflow",
        "right_answer": "text-shadow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following CSS property is used to specify whether the table cells share the common or separate border?",
        "answer_1": "border-radius",
        "answer_2": "border-collapse",
        "answer_3": "border-spacing",
        "answer_4": "None",
        "right_answer": "border-collapse"
    },
    {
        "question": "The HTML attribute used to define the inline styles is___________",
        "answer_1": "class",
        "answer_2": "styles",
        "answer_3": "style",
        "answer_4": "None of the above",
        "right_answer": "style"
    },
    {
        "question": "The CSS property used to draw a line around the elements outside the border?",
        "answer_1": "line",
        "answer_2": "border",
        "answer_3": "padding",
        "answer_4": "outline",
        "right_answer": "outline"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to select the p siblings of a div element?",
        "answer_1": "p",
        "answer_2": "div  p",
        "answer_3": "div + p",
        "answer_4": "div ~ p",
        "right_answer": "div ~p"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is used to specify the subscript of text using CSS?",
        "answer_1": "vertical-align: super",
        "answer_2": "vertical-align: sub",
        "answer_3": "vertical-align: subscript",
        "answer_4": "None",
        "right_answer": "vertical-align : sub"
    }
]